<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="als_info">
        Angular leaf spot is a bacterial disease. Heavy rains can drive the pathogen into leaves and cause
        significant problems in some fields. Spots appear angular when limited by leaf veins.  Symptoms of
        angular leaf spot usually first appear as water-soaked lesions bound by the veins of the leaf, so
        they are angular in shape. As they progress, the lesions may turn yellow and then brown and the leaf
        tissue may tear. Lesions may have yellow haloes. During wet weather, bacteria may ooze from the spots
        and later dry to a white residue chlorosis (yellowing) of the leaves.
    </string>

    <string name="bsh_info">
Black shank caused by the soilborne oomycete (fungal-like organism) Phytophthora nicotianae (Syn. Phytophthora parasitica)
        is one of the most destructive diseases on tobacco. Like other water molds, black shank is favored by high humidity
        or wet conditions and warm temperatures. P. nicotianae is polycyclic, and reproduces asexually and sexually.

Black shank can affect any part of the tobacco plant at any growth stage. Root and crown rot are the most common
        symptoms associated with P. nicotianae, but leaf spots may also be caused by this pathogen splashing from
        the soil onto leaf tissue. Leaf spots appear and form circular, yellowish-to-brown lesions up to 3 inches in
        diameter, with concentric rings, and are usually limited to lower leaves that are typically removed later in
        the growing season

    </string>

    <string name="bs_info">
The causal agent of brown spot is Alternaria alternata, which is an opportunistic pathogen of many crops. The pathogen
        survives in crop debris and disperses as conidia (asexual spores). Conidia germination requires moisture for
        germination and colonization of host tissue. Once tissues are colonized, abundant conidia are formed within
        lesions that are later dispersed to new tissues.

Small circular to irregularly-shaped spots, beginning small (0.25 in) and expanding as they mature (1.25 in).
        Lesions are dark brown with yellow halos surrounding the spots. Within the lesions, dark rings may be observed
        that contain thousands of spores that may be splash- or wind-dispersed to newer leaves. Lesions may coalesce,
        causing the necrotic tissue to tear away, leaving the leaves ragged. Brown spot can continue to develop under
        curing conditions, causing moldy growth on cured leaves.

    </string>
    <string name="lc_info">
Tobacco leaf curl disease (TLCD) is caused by begomoviruses in Geminiviridae, and infected plants exhibit leaf thickening,
        downward leaf curling, vein swelling as well as stunting symptoms. It is one of the economically important diseases
        in tropical and subtropical tobacco-growing areas.
    </string>
    <string name="pm_info">
Powdery mildew is a common fungus that affects a wide variety of plants. It is easily identified and appears as light grey
        or white powdery spots usually found on infected leaves, but can also be found underneath, or on stems, flowers,
        fruit or vegetables. The spots spread and will eventually cover most of the leaves on the plant, with new plant
        growth being most susceptible.

Powdery mildew thrives in warm, dry climates; however, it also needs fairly high humidity — like the warm days and cool
        nights in late spring to early summer. Not enough sunlight and poor air circulation also contribute to conditions
        that encourage powdery mildew.

Although rarely fatal, if left unchecked it can eventually cause serious harm to your plants by robbing it of water and
        nutrients. Most infections cause minor damage such as leaves turning yellow or becoming withered or distorted,
        but plants can also become weak, bloom less, and grow slower.

    </string>
    <string name="wf_info">
Soon after exposure to high levels of atmospheric pollutants, leaves may develop dark green water-soaked spots about 1/10
        inch in diameter. Within hours, the spots turn dark brown, sometimes remain brown, but often turn white within 48
        hours. Symptoms occur most often in low areas of fields. Plants are most sensitive when growing rapidly
        (plant bed and 4-6 weeks after transplanting), but symptoms may appear at any stage of growth. In the plant bed
        or on very sensitive varieties, spots appear over the entire leaf surface but are usually confined to the leaf
        tips of less sensitive varieties. Occasionally spots coalesce, or a central spot may be surrounded by smaller ones.
        Weather fleck is often confused with other flecks caused by chemicals, diseases, or nutritional disorders.
    </string>
</resources>