<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="als_mgmt">
        •	Practice early ploughing in nurseries\n
•	Use certified disease free seed\n
•	Rotate nursery sites and fields every 3 to 4 years with the following non-host crops such as groundnuts and maize.\n
•	Keep nursery and fields weed free to prevent alternative hosts from harbouring the pathogen inoculum.\n
•	Fumigate seedbeds - See yellow direct control column\n
•	Uproot and burn all infected plants soon after complete reaping tobacco to prevent spread of pathogen\n
•	There are currently no resistant varieties of tobacco against this disease\n
•	Avoid overhead irrigation as this can spread the bacterium\n

    </string>

    <string name="bsh_mgmt">
Selecting resistant varieties is the most economical management of this pathogen for tobacco growers.
        Since complete resistance to this disease is not available with recent race shifts, use of resistant
        varieties should be considered in combination with other management practices.
    </string>

    <string name="bs_mgmt">
Brown spot management is geared to reduce fungal inoculum build-up in the production system and delay initial onset
        of disease. Crop rotation away from tobacco will allow for crop debris to completely decay limiting fungal
        survival. Quickly destroying crop debris after harvest will also limit inoculum survival on tobacco tissues.

Infections by other pathogens that impact general plant health may also increase brown spot incidence. High nematode
        pressures, black shank, and Granville wilt may also increase brown spot. Limit nematode and other disease
        pressures where possible.
Adequate nutrition (not deficient nor excessive) for encouraging vigorous growth of leaves and limiting excess growth
        may reduce the impact of brown spot. Additionally, proper plant spacing and sucker control will limit humidity
        in plant canopies, reducing brown spot incidence.

    </string>

    <string name="lc_mgmt">
•	Remove and destroy the infected plants.\n
•	Rogue out the reservoir weed hosts which harbor the virus and whiteflies. Planting tobacco crops during the
        crop periods when the vector population is low.\n
•	Field sanitation.   \n
•	Highly contagious disease; washed the used implements as well as labor hands by running water.   \n
•	Balanced fertilizers are used (optimum Nitrogenous fertilizer).  \n

    </string>

    <string name="pm_mgmt">
•	Avoiding over fertilizing, overcrowding of plants and removal of affected basal leaves will help in minimizing
        primary infection and spread of the disease.\n
•	Early planting to escape cool temperature prevalent at the maturing stage will also reduce the incidence.\n
•	Apply sulphur powder (200 mesh) @ 40 kg/ha to soil between plant row 6-8 weeks after planting. Mix ash or sand
        to sulphur for easy application.\n
•	See that sulphur does not fall on tobacco leaves. Recommended for black soils only.\n
•	Spray 0.2% Karathane or Thiovit or 0.05% Carbendazim just before the disease sets in Repeat at 10-12 days
        interval if necessary.\n
•	Use resistant varieties like Swarna or Line 2359 developed at Central Tobacco Research Institute, in disease
        endemic area.\n
    </string>

    <string name="wf_mgmt">
Weather fleck deficiency can be corrected by application of nitrogenous fertilizer and recommended dose of nitrogen
        should be applied at the appropriate stage of plant growth for achieving maximum yield and desirable
        quality of tobacco.
    </string>
</resources>